Dear Human Resources Department of Step Media Company,

My name is Long, currently a UI UX Designer and HTML Developer at Vietnam Thuong Tin Trading Joint Stock Company - Vietbank, my current job includes designing website interface, software, Mobile app supporting Developer department. building user interface to serve internal needs of the Bank.

I heard that your company is recruiting for the position of UI UX Designer. With the orientation of becoming a Senior UI UX Designer and Frontend Developer, now I would like to send this letter, hope to arrange a meeting with your company to present the ability to meet the job as well as development orientation. develop yourself and your company.

Thanks and the Best regards,



SUMMARY

As a person who always wants to learn new things to improve myself and career.

With 9 years of experience in interface design and experience in building product interfaces, I am confident to complete the assigned independent work as well as teamwork.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth: 25/02/1987 Phone: 0977 98 1138

Email: tanlongduong@gmail.com

Address: 99/16 TL41 Street, Thanh Loc Ward, District 12

SKILLS

Design tools: Photoshop, Illustrator,

After effects, adobe XD, Figma Coding: HTML, CSS, Javascript,

ReactJS, Bootstrap, MUI,

Wordpress

Soft skills: I have ability to self-manage work, self learn,

work independently and in groups.

HOBBIES

Football, search for information

DƯƠNG TẤN LONG

UX UI Design, HTML Developer

EDUCATION

Industrial University of Ho Chi Minh City

Major: Information technology

Certificate: Layout website, Vector graphics.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020 - Present

Vietbank Thuong Tin Commercial Joint Stock Bank

Position: UX/UI Designer - HTML Developer

Website: vietbank.com.vn

Address: 62A CMT 8 Street, Vo Thi Sau Ward, District 3

2018 - 2020

Lac Viet Joint Stock Company

Position: UX/UI Designer - HTML Developer

Website: accnet.vn

Address: 23 Nguyen Thi Huynh Street,

Ward 8, Phu Nhuan District

2017 - 2018

FreeSale Viet Nam Company

Position: HTML Developer

Website: vietry.com.vn

Address: 6 Nguyen Thi Minh Khai Street,

ĐaKao Ward. District 1

2013 - 2017

Twin Joint Stock Company

Position: Team Leader Designer

Website: twin.vn

Address: 63A Vo Van Tan Street, Ward 6, District 3